<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShopMe</string>
    <string name="shopping_bag_illustration_description">A full shopping bag with animated grocery characters</string>
    <string name="close_action_button_description">Close button</string>
    <string name="add_action_button_description">Add button</string>
    <string name="aldi_logo_description">Aldi logo</string>
    <string name="dm_logo_description">dm logo</string>
    <string name="edeka_logo_description">Edeka logo</string>
    <string name="kaufland_logo_description">Kaufland logo</string>
    <string name="lidl_logo_description">Lidl logo</string>
    <string name="mueller_logo_description">Müller logo</string>
    <string name="netto_logo_description">Netto logo</string>
    <string name="norma_logo_description">Norma logo</string>
    <string name="rewe_logo_description">Rewe logo</string>
    <string name="rossmann_logo_description">Rossmann logo</string>
    <string name="tomato_illustration_description">A cute animated tomato character with big eyes and a smile</string>
    <string name="carrot_illustration_description">A cute animated carrot character with green leaves and a big smile</string>
    <string name="microphone_illustration_description">A cute animated microphone character with big eyes and a smile</string>
    <string name="bakery_illustration_description">A group of cute animated bakery items: a baguette, a muffin, a donut, and a croissant</string>
    <string name="canned_food_illustration_description">Three cute animated cans: peas, tomato, and tuna, with expressive faces and open lids</string>
    <string name="bread_illustration_description">A freshly baked loaf of bread in a basket with green beans on the side</string>
    <string name="whole_grain_bakery_illustration_description">A collection of cute bakery items including a flour bag, bread loaf, croissant, and grains, all with happy faces</string>
    <string name="cheese_illustration_description">A cute animated cheese wedge with big eyes, a smile, and cheese holes</string>
    <string name="soda_illustration_description">A cute animated soda bottle character with a happy face, surrounded by bubbles and green olives</string>
    <string name="beverages_illustration_description">A group of cute animated drink characters: a soda bottle, a coffee cup, and an orange juice glass with ice and orange slices</string>
    <string name="fish_illustration_description">A cute animated blue fish on a bed of lettuce with tomatoes, lemon slices, and a fish skeleton</string>
    <string name="frozen_food_illustration_description">A blue cooler bag filled with various cute animated frozen food items: fish sticks, peas, shrimp, pizza, and ice cream</string>
    <string name="ready_meal_illustration_description">A group of cute animated ready meal characters: ramen cup, pizza box, and a meal tray with mashed potatoes and meatballs</string>
    <string name="fruit_characters_illustration_description">A colorful group of happy animated fruit characters including an apple, banana, grapes, and others</string>
    <string name="meat_illustration_description">A group of cute animated meat characters: a steak, a bacon slice, and a sausage, with expressive faces and garnish</string>
    <string name="salami_illustration_description">A cute animated salami character with a shocked face and two slices in front</string>
    <string name="dairy_alternatives_illustration_description">A group of cute animated dairy alternative characters: almond milk carton, oat milk bottle, coconut, and grain sack</string>
    <string name="dairy_illustration_description">A group of cute animated dairy products: milk, cheese, yogurt, eggs, and butter.</string>
    <string name="pasta_illustration_description">A group of happy pasta characters: a bag of penne, a bundle of spaghetti with a red ribbon, and macaroni pieces on the ground</string>
    <string name="oils_illustration_description">A group of happy animated oil bottles and seeds, including olive oil and sunflower oil with cheerful faces</string>
    <string name="rice_illustration_description">A happy animated rice sack and a bowl of rice with friendly faces and a wooden scoop</string>
    <string name="sauces_illustration_description">A trio of happy animated sauce bottles: ketchup, mustard, and hot sauce, with fresh ingredients like tomatoes, peppers, and garlic</string>
    <string name="fish_sticks_label">FISH STICKS</string>
    <string name="peas_label">PEAS</string>
    <string name="shrimp_label">SHRIMP</string>
    <string name="pizza_label">PIZZA</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_label">ICE</string>
    <string name="almond_milk_label">ALMOND\nMILK</string>
    <string name="oat_milk_label">OAT\nMILK</string>
    <string name="milch_label">MILCH</string>
    <string name="joghurt_label">JOGHURT</string>
    <string name="nudeln_label">NUDELN</string>
    <string name="reis_label">REIS</string>
    <string name="mustard_label">MUSTARD</string>
    <string name="hot_sauce_label">HOT\nSAUCE</string>
    <string name="snacks_illustration_description">A group of happy animated snack characters: soda, chips, chocolate, and popcorn</string>
    <string name="sweets_illustration_description">A colorful group of happy animated sweets characters including a cupcake, cookie, chocolate bar, and lollipop</string>
    <string name="chips_label">CHIPS</string>
    <string name="spices_illustration_description">A group of happy animated spice characters: salt shaker, paprika jar, oil bottle, chili peppers, garlic, and a bowl of spices</string>
    <string name="paprika_label">PAPRIKA</string>
    <string name="standard_label">STANDARD</string>
    <string name="standard_badge_description">A golden checkmark with a crown and a blue ribbon labeled STANDARD, surrounded by stars and leaves.</string>
    <string name="vegan_illustration_description">A colorful group of happy animated vegan characters including an avocado, tofu, plant milk, and a tomato, with a large green VEGAN ribbon.</string>
    <string name="plant_milk_label">PLANT\nMILK</string>
    <string name="vegan_label">VEGAN</string>
    <string name="veggie_label">VEGGIE</string>
    <string name="veggie_illustration_description">A colorful group of happy animated veggie characters including a broccoli, burger, carrot, tofu, milk and a tomato, with a large wooden VEGGIE ribbon and a checkmark.</string>
    <string name="vegetables_group_illustration_description">A colorful group of happy animated vegetable characters including a tomato, carrot, corn, and others</string>
    <string name="out_of_time_illustration_description">A worried animated alarm clock with an hourglass, indicating running out of time</string>
    <string name="sync_success_illustration_description">Illustration showing two happy smartphones with arrows and a checkmark, indicating a successful synchronization.</string>
    <string name="sync_error_illustration_description">Illustration showing a laptop and a smartphone with worried faces, circular arrows, and a warning triangle, indicating a synchronization error.</string>
</resources>
